<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">

  <title><![CDATA[Awin Abi]]></title>
  <link href="http://awin.github.com/atom.xml" rel="self"/>
  <link href="http://awin.github.com/"/>
  <updated>2012-06-17T20:07:36+05:30</updated>
  <id>http://awin.github.com/</id>
  <author>
    <name><![CDATA[Awin Abi]]></name>
  </author>

  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Rain]]></title>
    <link href="http://awin.github.com/rain"/>
    <updated>2011-02-20T00:00:00+05:30</updated>
    <id>http://awin.github.com/rain</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<pre><code>was an admired accomplishment a long time ago!</code></pre>

<p>Then suddenly the chilled rain poured out. Every summer end Babuli would ask God to bring a good rain, a good climate, and will wait rather painstrikenly till the first rain of the year falls. He needed it bring with it a calming blanket of coolness around him and he very well knew that it would never forget to bring that eastern wind; but this year he did not expect so much of it - just enough to fly his shawl from his shoulder back and forth. It was rain that added color to the much dull, inactive and lonely life of Babuli.</p>
<p class="more"><a href="/rain">Read the full article</a></p>]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Your side project is growing]]></title>
    <link href="http://awin.github.com/your-side-project-is-growing"/>
    <updated>2011-02-16T00:00:00+05:30</updated>
    <id>http://awin.github.com/your-side-project-is-growing</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>So you are thinking of developing an application, in your free time! Yes you are in the right track. There are millions of side businesses, working around small niches and making profit. Put in 4 hrs a week and over a year you have a great application(provided you create something what people want) that is useful for others and more importantly, a application that people doesn&#8217;t hesitate to pay for, if you wish to monetize your app. Target the Fortune 5 million as <a href='http://37signals.com/svn/archives2/sidebusiness_software_the_neglected_software_market.php'>this blog says</a>.</p>
<p class="more"><a href="/your-side-project-is-growing">Read the full article</a></p>]]></content>
  </entry>
  
</feed>